<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Contribution on BCTS</title>
    <link>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/contribution/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Contribution on BCTS</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;{year}, All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 00:34:39 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/contribution/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Activities</title>
        <link>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/contribution/activities/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:10:48 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/contribution/activities/</guid>
        <description> IEEE Blockchain Newsletter特邀编委 CCGrid BCTS区块链技术与系统研讨会程序委员会主席，2020. 第七届CCF大数据学术会议宣传主席，2019. IEEE MSN宣传主席，2019. BlockApp区块链技术与应用研讨会程序委员会主席，2019. IEEE ICPADS BCTS区块链技术与系统研讨会程序委员会主席，2017，2018.  </description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Aplications</title>
        <link>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/contribution/applications/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:10:48 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/contribution/applications/</guid>
        <description>( BookChain ) The current mobile bookcrossing system generally has problems such as lack of trust, ineffective supervision, and low circulation efficiency, which have seriously affected the normal operation of bookcrossing. BookChain integrates bookcrossing activities with emerging blockchain technology, leverages the open, transparent, traceable, and decentralized characteristics of the blockchain to record the circulation information of books on the chain, so that participants can trace the historical circulation records of books, greatly reducing the possibility of losing books and rebuilding the trust in bookcrossing.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Awards</title>
        <link>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/contribution/awards/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:10:48 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/contribution/awards/</guid>
        <description> The 14th International Conference on Green, Pervasive, and Cloud Computing (GPC) 会议唯一最佳论文奖，2019. 金链盟中国区块链应用大赛优秀创意奖，2018.  </description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Evaluation Tools</title>
        <link>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/contribution/evaluation-tools/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:10:48 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/contribution/evaluation-tools/</guid>
        <description>BlockSim ( BlockSim ) A blockchain network simulator, which can be used for blockchain network protocol verification.
BlockSim has been developed with extreme scalability and support for network dynamically change in mind. It is composed of the event-driven engine, which is supported by many simple, extendable, and pluggable components (i.e., simulation-network, simulation-consensus, and simulation-data). BlockSim supports structured and unstructured Blockchain P2P network simulation. To simulate different network environments in the blockchain, developers can implement the interfaces provided by BlockSim as needed, which include topological connection, latency setting, network broadcast algorithm and so on.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Patents</title>
        <link>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/contribution/patents/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:10:48 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/contribution/patents/</guid>
        <description> 肖江，戴小海，杨文辉，金海，一种适用于以太坊的用户画像构建方法及系统，专利号：201911295828.3，2020-1-15，中国. 肖江，曾家杰，戴小海，杨文辉，郝威峰，王超凡，金海，一种基于区块链技术的图书漂流方法及系统，专利号：201911133428.2，2019-12-23，中国. 陆枫，甘露，肖江，金海，胡侃，一种基于区块链的数据读写方法及区块链网络结构，专利号：201910323667.8，2019-4-22，中国. 肖江, 杨文辉，戴小海，金海，一种基于DAG的区块链的跨链交互方法和系统，专利号：201911099003.4，2019-1-19，中国.  </description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Projects</title>
        <link>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/contribution/projects/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:10:48 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/contribution/projects/</guid>
        <description>Basic Structure ![basic structure](https://bctsgroup.github.io/images/contributions/basic structure.jpg)
Data model  ( Jidar ) We propose a novel Jigsaw-like Data Reduction (Jidar) approach. Each node in Jidar only stores transactions of interest and relevant Merkle branches from the complete blocks, just like selecting several pieces from the jigsaw puzzles. A node can maintain and verify all its relevant data locally and safely without any trust assumptions. To verify the validity of a newly proposed transaction, Merkle branches relevant to the inputs are provided along with the transaction by the proposer.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Publications</title>
        <link>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/contribution/publications/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:10:48 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/contribution/publications/</guid>
        <description>Xiaohai Dai, Jiang Xiao, Wenhui Yang, Chaofan Wang, Jian Chang, Rui Han, Hai Jin, “LVQ: A Lightweight Verifiable Query Approach for Transaction History in Bitcoin“, IEEE ICDCS, Singapore, 2020. Weifeng Hao, Jiajie Zeng, Xiaohai Dai, Jiang Xiao, Qiang-Sheng Hua, Hanhua Chen, Kuan-Ching Li, Hai Jin, “[Towards A Trust-Enhanced Blockchain P2P Topology for Enabling Fast and Reliable Broadcast](https://bctsgroup.github.io/pdf/towards blockchainp2p.pdf)”, IEEE TNSM, 2020. Wenhui Yang, Xiaohai Dai, Jiang Xiao, Hai Jin, “LDV: A Lightweight DAG-based Blockchain for Vehicular Social Networks“, IEEE TVT, 2020.</description>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>