<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BCTS</title>
    <link>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on BCTS</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;{year}, All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 04:15:05 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://BCTSGroup.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
      
      <item>
        <title>2021 Fall</title>
        <link>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/2021/2021_fall/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 00:10:48 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/2021/2021_fall/</guid>
        <description>   Date Lecturers Paper title Conference Slides     20211012 Hanrui Pyramid: A Layered Sharding Blockchain System INFOCOM&#39;21 Download   20211019 Shijie SlimChain: Scaling Blockchain Transactions through Off-Chain Storage and Parallel Processing VLDB&#39;21 Download   20211019 Shuohua A Weak Consensus Algorithm and Its Application to High-Performance Blockchain INFOCOM&#39;21 Download   20211026 Chengfeng User Distributions in Shard-based Blockchain Network- Queueing Modeling, Game Analysis, and Protocol Design MobiHoc&#39;21 Download   20211026 Jingtao Prism: Deconstructing the Blockchain to Approach Physical Limits PODC&#39;21 Download   20211102 Junpei An Off-The-Chain Execution Environment for Scalable Testing and Profiling of Smart Contracts ATC&#39;21 Download   20211109 Changjian Bringing Decentralized Search to Decentralized Services OSDI&#39;21 Download   20211116 Chenchen The Anatomy of a Cryptocurrency Pump-and-Dump Scheme Security’19 Download   20211116 Minrui Investigating MMM Ponzi Scheme on Bitcoin CCS’20 Download   20211123 Bingru All You Need is DAG PODC&#39;21 Download   20211123 Yifei Towards Understanding Cryptocurrency Derivatives:A Case Study of BitMEX WWW&#39;21 Download   20211130 Enping PEEP: A Parallel Execution Engine for Permissioned Blockchain Systems DASFAA&#39;21 Download   20211130 Binhong Authenticated Range Query Using SGX for Blockchain Light Clients DASFAA&#39;20 Download    </description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>2020 Fall</title>
        <link>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/2020/2020_fall/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:10:48 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/2020/2020_fall/</guid>
        <description>   Date Lecturers Paper title Conference Slides     20200902 Chenchen Li A Data Science Approach for Detecting Honeypots in Ethereum ICBC&#39;20 Download   20200902 Jiajie Zeng Hyperledger Fabric – Network - Download   20200917 Shijie Zhang Erlay: Efficient Transaction Relay for Bitcoin CCS&#39;19 Download   20200917 Xiaohai Dai Fabric数据层及其他介绍 - Download   20200921 Rui Han Hyperledger transaction flow - Download   20200924 Jian Chang HotRing: A Hotspot-Aware In- Memory Key-Value Store FAST&#39;20 Download   20201009 Rui Han HyperService: Interoperability and Programmability Across Heterogeneous Blockchain CCS&#39;19 Download   20201105 Junpei Ni The Honey Badger of BFT Protocols CCS&#39;16 Download   20201105 Jian Chang Smart Contract in Fabric - Download   20201112 Shuohua Dong Searching an Encrypted Cloud Meets Blockchain: A Decentralized, Reliable and Fair Realization INFOCOM&#39;18 Download   20201118 Jiajie Zhang Shrec: bandwidth-efficient transaction relay in high-throughput blockchain systems SoCC&#39;20 Download   20201119 Shijie Zhang Hyperledger Cactus - Download   20201126 Xiaohai Dai Research on Blockchain- A Summary - Download   20201126 Wenhui Yang 图示区块链总结 - Download   20201203 Chaofan Wang SkyChain:A Deep Reinforcement Learning-Empowered Dynamic Blockchain Sharding System ICPP&#39;20 Download   20201210 Chenchen Li Understanding Ethereum via Graph Analysis INFOCOM&#39;18 Download   20201210 Junpei Ni Paxos made Simple ACM Sigact News, 2001 Download   20201216 Shuohua Dong Blockene: A High Throughput Blockchain over Mobile Devices OSDI&#39;20 Download   20201218 Shijie Zhang Byzantine Ordere Consensus without Byzantine Oligarchy OSDI&#39;20 Download    </description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>2020 Spring</title>
        <link>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/2020/2020_spring/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:10:48 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/2020/2020_spring/</guid>
        <description>Date Lecturers Paper title Conference Slides     20200302 Rui Han RepChain: A Reputation-based Secure, Fast and High Incentive Blockchain System via Sharding IoTJ&#39;20 Download   20200312 Jian Chang FAST: Fast Architecture Sensitive Tree Search on Modern CPUs and GPUs SGMOD&#39;10 Download   20200318 Chenchen Li Who Are the Phishers? Phishing Scam Detection on Ethereum via Network Embedding TSMC&#39;20 Download   20200326 Chaofan Wang Market Manipulation of Bitcoin: Evidence from Mining the Mt.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>2021 Spring</title>
        <link>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/2021/2021_spring/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:10:48 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/2021/2021_spring/</guid>
        <description>   Date Lecturers Paper title Conference Slides     20210225 Jiajie Zeng FSTR-Funds Skewness Aware Transaction Routing DSN&#39;20 Download   20210225 Xiaohai Dai HotStuff- BFT Consensus with Linearity and Responsiveness PODC&#39;19 Download   20210304 Rui Han LedgerDB - a centralized ledger database for universal audit and verification VLDB&#39;20 Download   20210311 Bingru Si Perigee-Efficient Peer-to-Peer Network Design for Blockchains PODC&#39;20 Download   20210311 Shuohua Dong High Throughput Cryptocurrency Routing in Payment Channel Networks NSDI&#39;20 Download   20210318 Junpei Ni Ghostor- Toward a Secure Data-Sharing System from Decentral-ized Trust NSDI&#39;20 Download   20210318 Feng Cheng ResilientDB-GlobalScaleResilientBlockchain Fabric VLDB‘20 Download   20210325 Xiaohai Dai Dumbo: Faster Asynchronous BFT Protocols CCS&#39;20 Download   20210325 Chenchen Li Tight Consistency Bounds for Bitcoin CCS;20 -   20210401 Jian Chang Ekiden: A Platform for Confidentiality- Preserving, Trustworthy, and Performant Smart Contracts S&amp;amp;P&#39;20 Download   20210401 Shijie Zhang SBFT: a Scalable and Decentralized Trust Infrastructure DSN&#39;20 Download   20210408 Rui Han BFT-Store: Storage partition for permis- sioned blockchain via erasure coding ICDE&#39;20 Download   20210408 Jingtao Yue OHIE: Blockchain Scaling Made Simple S&amp;amp;P&#39;20 Download   20210415 Bingru Si Fair and Efficient Gos- sip in Hyperledger Fab-ric ICDCS&#39;20 Download   20210415 Shuohua Dong EPIC: Efficient Asyn-chronous BFT with Adaptive Security DSN&#39;20 Download   20210422 Junpei Ni Blockchain Based Auditable Access Control for Distributed Business Processes ICDCS&#39;20 Download   20210429 Feng Chen Mneme: A Mobile Distributed Ledger INFOCOM&#39;20 Download   20210429 Xiaohai Dai Zyzzyva- speculative Byzantine fault tolerance SOSP&#39;07 Download   20210513 Chenchen Li Towards Understand- ing and Demystifying Bitcoin Mixing Services WWW&#39;21 Download   20210513 Jian Chang BITE: Bitcoin Lightweight Client Privacy using Trusted Execution USENIX Security&#39;19 Download   20210520 Shijie Zhang Microsecond Consen- sus for Microsecond Applications OSDI&#39;20 Download   20210520 Rui Han Enabling Reliable Key- word Search in En- crypted Decentralized Storage with Fairness TDSC&#39;18 Download   20210527 JIngtai Yue Sync HotStuff: Sim- ple and Practical Synchronous State Ma- chine Replication SP&#39;20 Download   20210603 Bingru Si Graphene: Efficient Interactive Set Rec- onciliation Applied to Blockchain Propagation SIGCOMM&#39;19 Download   20210603 Junpei Ni Droplet: Decentralized Authorization and Access Control for En- crypted Data Streams USENIX Security&#39;20 Download   20210610 Shuohua Dong Mneme A Mobile Distributed Ledger INFOCOM&#39;20 Download   20210617 Feng Cheng CycLedger A Scalable and Secure Parral Pro- tocol for Distributed Ledger via Sharding IPDPS&#39;20 Download   20210701 Xiaohai Dai DenseChain: Faster Transaction Processing in Public Blockchains ATC&#39;21 Download       Download    </description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>2022 Fall</title>
        <link>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/2022/2022_fall/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:10:48 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/2022/2022_fall/</guid>
        <description>Date Lecturers Paper title Conference Slides     20220823 Bingru TIPS: Transaction Inclusion Protocol with Signaling in DAG-based Blockchain JSAC&#39;22 Download   20220907 Yuandi Bullshark: DAG BFT Protocols Made Practical CCS&#39;22 Download   20220909 Chuwu BitcoinHeist: Topological Data Analysis for Ransomware Detection on the Bitcoin Blockchain  Download   20220914 Licheng ALEX: An Updatable Adaptive Learned Index SIGMOD&#39;20 Download   20220916 Chenchen A2MM: Mitigating Frontrunning, Transaction Reordering and Consensus Instability in Decentralized Exchanges  Download   20220920 Yifan Mixing Transactions with Arbitrary Values on Blockchains ICDE&#39;22 Download   20220923 Chenchen Token Spammers, Rug Pulls, and SniperBots: An Analysis of the?</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>2022 Spring</title>
        <link>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/2022/2022_spring/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:10:48 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/research/2022/2022_spring/</guid>
        <description>Date Lecturers Paper title Conference Slides     20220301 Liping Bidl- A High-throughput, Low-latency Permissioned Blockchain Framework for Datacenter Networks SOSP&#39;21 Download   20220308 Enping FASTBLOCK: Accelerating Blockchains via Hardware Transactional Memory ICDCS&#39;21 Download   20220308 Shijie Scaling Blockchains Using Pipelined Execution and Sparse Peers SoCC’21 Download   20220315 Shuohua Leaderless Consensus ICDCS’21 Download   20220315 Zhaonan Kauri: Scalable BFT Consensus with Pipelined Tree-Based Dissemination and Aggregation SOSP&#39;21 Download   20220322 Jingtao SharPer: Sharding Permissioned Blockchains Over Network Clusters SIGMOD&#39;21 Download   20220322 Chengfeng Elastic Resource Allocation against Imbalanced Transaction Assignments in Sharding-based Permissioned Blockchains TPDS&#39;22 Download   20220402 Changjian Authenticated Keyword Search in Scalable Hybrid-Storage Blockchains ICDE&#39;21 Download   20220412 Chenchen On the Just-In-Time Discovery of Profit-Generating Transactions in DeFi Protocols S&amp;amp;P&#39;21 Download   20220412 Yifei Smart Contract Vulnerabilities: Vulnerable Does Not Imply Exploited USENIX Security&#39;21 Download   20220419 Minrui High-Frequency Trading on Decentralized On-Chain Exchanges S&amp;amp;P&#39;21 Download   20220419 Bingru Accelerating Transactions Relay in Blockchain Networks via Reputation IWQoS&#39;21 Download   20220524 Binhong P2B-Trace- Privacy-Preserving Blockchain-based Contact Tracing to Combat Pandemics SIGMOD&#39;21 Download   20220524 Liping Revisiting Optimal Resilience of Fast Byzantine Consensus PODC&#39;21 Download   20220531 Shijie Proteus: Autonomous Adaptive Storage for Mixed Workloads SIGMOD&#39;22 Download   20220531 Enping Why Do My Blockchain Transactions Fail?</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Papers</title>
        <link>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/publications/papers/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:10:48 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/publications/papers/</guid>
        <description>(*=corresponding author)
 Hai Jin, Chenchen Li, Jiang Xiao*, Teng Zhang, Xiaohai Dai, and Bo Li. Detecting Arbitrage on Ethereum Through Feature Fusion and Positive-Unlabeled Learning. In IEEE Journal on Selected Areas in Communications (JSAC 2022). 2022. DOI: 10.1109/JSAC.2022.3213335（CCF A） Jiang Xiao, Shijie Zhang, Zhiwei Zhang, Bo Li, Xiaohai Dai, and Hai Jin. Nezha: Exploiting Concurrency for Transaction Processing in DAG-based Blockchains, In Proceedings of 42nd IEEE International Conferene on Distributed Computing Systems (IEEE ICDCS), 2022.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Research projects</title>
        <link>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/projects/research-projects/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:10:48 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/projects/research-projects/</guid>
        <description>Basic Structure ![basic structure](https://bctsgroup.github.io/images/contributions/basic structure.jpg)
Data model  ( Jidar ) We propose a novel Jigsaw-like Data Reduction (Jidar) approach. Each node in Jidar only stores transactions of interest and relevant Merkle branches from the complete blocks, just like selecting several pieces from the jigsaw puzzles. A node can maintain and verify all its relevant data locally and safely without any trust assumptions. To verify the validity of a newly proposed transaction, Merkle branches relevant to the inputs are provided along with the transaction by the proposer.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Aplications</title>
        <link>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/projects/applications/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:10:48 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/projects/applications/</guid>
        <description>( BookChain ) The current mobile bookcrossing system generally has problems such as lack of trust, ineffective supervision, and low circulation efficiency, which have seriously affected the normal operation of bookcrossing. BookChain integrates bookcrossing activities with emerging blockchain technology, leverages the open, transparent, traceable, and decentralized characteristics of the blockchain to record the circulation information of books on the chain, so that participants can trace the historical circulation records of books, greatly reducing the possibility of losing books and rebuilding the trust in bookcrossing.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Patents</title>
        <link>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/publications/patents/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:10:48 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/publications/patents/</guid>
        <description> 肖江，戴小海，杨文辉，金海，一种适用于以太坊的用户画像构建方法及系统，专利号：201911295828.3，2020-1-15，中国. 肖江，曾家杰，戴小海，杨文辉，郝威峰，王超凡，金海，一种基于区块链技术的图书漂流方法及系统，专利号：201911133428.2，2019-12-23，中国. 陆枫，甘露，肖江，金海，胡侃，一种基于区块链的数据读写方法及区块链网络结构，专利号：201910323667.8，2019-4-22，中国. 肖江, 杨文辉，戴小海，金海，一种基于DAG的区块链的跨链交互方法和系统，专利号：201911099003.4，2019-1-19，中国. 肖江；曾家杰，张世桀，金海，基于区块链跨链交互的动态覆盖网络拓扑构建方法及装置，申请号： 202011421191.0, 中国. 陆枫，甘露，肖江，金海，胡侃，一种基于区块链的数据读写方法及区块链网络结构 2019-4-22, 中国, 专利号：2019103236678.  </description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Awards</title>
        <link>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/publications/awards/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:10:48 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/publications/awards/</guid>
        <description> The 14th International Conference on Green, Pervasive, and Cloud Computing (GPC) 会议唯一最佳论文奖，2019. 金链盟中国区块链应用大赛优秀创意奖，2018.  </description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Evaluation Tools</title>
        <link>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/projects/evaluation-tools/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:10:48 +0900</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/projects/evaluation-tools/</guid>
        <description>BlockSim A blockchain network simulator, which can be used for blockchain network protocol verification.
BlockSim has been developed with extreme scalability and support for network dynamically change in mind. It is composed of the event-driven engine, which is supported by many simple, extendable, and pluggable components (i.e., simulation-network, simulation-consensus, and simulation-data). BlockSim supports structured and unstructured Blockchain P2P network simulation. To simulate different network environments in the blockchain, developers can implement the interfaces provided by BlockSim as needed, which include topological connection, latency setting, network broadcast algorithm and so on.</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
        <link>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/blog/markdown-syntax/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/blog/markdown-syntax/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Lorem est tota propiore conpellat pectoribus de&lt;br /&gt;
pectora summo. Redit teque digerit hominumque toris verebor lumina non cervice&lt;br /&gt;
subde tollit usus habet Arctonque, furores quas nec ferunt. Quoque montibus nunc&lt;br /&gt;
caluere tempus&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Rich Content</title>
        <link>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/blog/rich-content/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 10 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/blog/rich-content/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Lorem est tota propiore conpellat pectoribus de&lt;br /&gt;
pectora summo. Redit teque digerit hominumque toris verebor lumina non cervice&lt;br /&gt;
subde tollit usus habet Arctonque, furores quas nec ferunt. Quoque montibus nunc&lt;br /&gt;
caluere tempus&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Placeholder Text</title>
        <link>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/blog/placeholder-text/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/blog/placeholder-text/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Lorem est tota propiore conpellat pectoribus de&lt;br /&gt;
pectora summo. Redit teque digerit hominumque toris verebor lumina non cervice&lt;br /&gt;
subde tollit usus habet Arctonque, furores quas nec ferunt. Quoque montibus nunc&lt;br /&gt;
caluere tempus&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      </item>
      
      <item>
        <title>Emoji Support</title>
        <link>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/blog/emoji-support/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://BCTSGroup.github.io/blog/emoji-support/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Lorem est tota propiore conpellat pectoribus de&lt;br /&gt;
pectora summo. Redit teque digerit hominumque toris verebor lumina non cervice&lt;br /&gt;
subde tollit usus habet Arctonque, furores quas nec ferunt. Quoque montibus nunc&lt;br /&gt;
caluere tempus&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>